《迷失》前情提要
Previously on "lost"...
你好  Ben
Hello, Ben.
-你还活着  -是的
- You're alive. - Yes, I am.
你说你知道怎么找到他们吗  找到Jin
Are you saying you know how to find them? How to find Jin?
我有些主意
I have some ideas.
这么说你是知道的
So you knew
如果我们带他回来  这会发生在Locke身上
This would happen to Locke if we brought him back here?
死者已矣
Dead is dead.
你不可能让他们复活的
You don't get come back from that.
在天鹅站的那些达摩组织的人
The Dharma folks at the swan work site--
他们会钻到地下
They're gonna drill into the ground
并且无意中触发一股巨大的能量
And accidentally tap into a massive pocket of energy,
那会导致你们的飞机  大洋航班815号
And that will cause your plane-- oceanic 815--
坠毁在这岛上
To crash on this island.
我想我可以中和掉那股能量
I think I can negate that energy.
如果成功的话  那个船舱就不会建造
If I can, then that hatch will never be built,
然后你们的飞机会按原计划着陆
And your plane will land just like it's supposed to.
那你具体是怎么计划破坏这股能量的呢
And just how exactly do you plan on destroying this energy?
我要引爆一颗氢弹
I'm gonna detonate a hydrogen bomb.
Richard  炸弹在哪  在哪里
Where's the bomb, Richard? Where is it?
我要你的人去埋起来的那颗氢弹
The hydrogen bomb that I told your people to bury.
藏在哪里
Where is it?
听我说  把枪放下  我们好好谈  行吧
Listen to me. lower your gun, and we'll talk. okay?
没必要要伤人  把枪放下吧
Nobody has to get hurt here. Just put the gun down.
我会给你3秒钟考虑
I'm gonna give you three seconds.
-一  -别这样
- One... - Don't do this.
他在那干什么呢
What's he doing down there?
Jack  他疯了  是吗
Jack, he's crazy. is he?
如果这正是我们在这里的原因会怎么样
What if this is why we're here?
如果这是我们唯一的机会
What if this is our one chance
把事情还原成他们的本来面目
To put things back the way they're supposed to be?
不  你以为你想做什么呢
No. What the hell do you think you're doing?!
他们开枪打了他  我要去帮忙
They shot him! I'm gonna go help.
是的  他们也会开枪打你的
Yeah, they're gonna shoot you too.
我们必须走  Jack  现在就得走
We have to go, Jack. We have to go now.
-Jack  -不准动
- Jack! - Don't you move!
不准动
Don't move.
你到底是谁
Just who the bloody hell might you be?
Eloise
Eloise!
发生了什么事
What happened?
这人走进营地  用枪指着我的脑袋
This man walked into camp and put a gun to my head,
然后Eloise反击了  你在哪发现他们
And Eloise... reacted. Where'd you find them?
蹲在草丛里面  象老鼠一样
Crouched in the bushes... like rats.
你们是和这个人一起的吗
Did you two come here with this man?
是的
Yes.
把他们关进我的帐篷
Put them in my tent.
你愿意告诉我吗  Eloise
Would you care to tell me, Eloise,
为什么达摩组织似乎要对我们宣战呢
Why the Dharma initiative seems to have declared war on us?
这些人不是来自达摩组织的  Charles
These people aren't from the dharma initiative, Charles.
那他们从哪里来
Then where the hell are they from?
三十年后
thirty years later
Richard  他来了
Richard, he's here.
我带来了晚餐
I brought dinner.
John
John?
你好  Richard
Hello, Richard.
好久不见
It's been a while.
有三年了吧
It's--it's been, uh, three years.
发生了什么事  你去了哪里
What happened? What--where--where were you?
我会在路上解释
I'll explain on the way.
去哪里的路上
On the way where?
快要到晚上了
It's gonna be night soon.
你和我有任务要执行
You and I have an errand to run,
我们没有太多时间
And we don't have a lot of time.
怎么了
What's wrong?
你有些不一样
Something different about you.
我现在有目标了
I have a purpose now.
他在这干嘛呢
What's he doing here?
他帮我回到这里的
He helped me get back.
为什么Locke说这些是他的手下
Why did Locke say these were his people?
我以为是你的手下
I thought they were yours.
当我离开这岛的时候  John来了
When I left the island, John stepped in.
他现在是这里的头
He's the leader now.
跟他说话的人是谁
Who's that man he's talking to?
他叫Richard Alpert
His name is richard alpert.
他有点像
He's a kind of...
军师
Advisor.
而且他做那份差事很久很久了
And he has had that job for a very very long time
Sun  你在
Sun? What are you...
1977年的时候你在这里吗
Were you here in 1977?
你说什么
Excuse me?
这些人
These people...
Jack Shephard  Kate Austen  Hugo Reyes
Jack Shephard, Kate Austen, Hugo Reyes.
他们和我的丈夫在这里
They were here with my husband--
Jin Kwon
Jin Kwon.
你在这里吗
Were you here?
你记得他们吗  随便是谁
Do you remember them? A-any of them?
是的  30年前我在这里
Yes, I was here 30 years ago.
而且我确实记得这些人
And I do. I remember these people.
我记得非常清楚和他们的见面  因为
I remember meeting them very clearly, because...
我亲眼看着他们都死了
I watched them all die.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧下载 请登陆www.YYeTs.net
翻译：冰卡    非燕    zhjing    发疯    牛牛
时间轴：龚轴人
校对：Afan   非燕  许愿
总监：非燕
要喝水吗
Drink of water?
你说这是真的吗
Do you think it's true?
他们都死了吗
They're all dead?
我认为我们回来不会一无所获的  Sun
I don't think we went through all this for nothing, Sun.
我准备好了  John
I'm ready, John.
我给你的指南针你还留着吗
You still have that compass I gave you?
有点生锈了  但还能找准方向
A little rusty, but she can still find north.
Ben  你能跟我们一起走就好了
Ben, I'd appreciate it if you'd join us.
怎么了  难道你对我和过去的下属在一起不放心吗
What, John, don't you trust me here with my former people?
担心我搞突然袭击吗
Afraid I'll stage a coup?
你再耍什么花招  我也无所畏惧
I'm not afraid of anything you can do anymore, Ben.
这样的话  我愿意加入
Well, in that case, i'd love to come.
很好
Good.
留在原地  我们几小时后回来
Stay here. we'll be back in a couple of hours.
希望能有所发现
I'll see what I can find out.
Sun  无论发生什么事  我向你保证
But whatever happens, sun,you have my word.
如果有办法能使你和Jin能够重聚
If there's a way for you and Jin to be together again,
如果能够找到拯救我们的人的方法
If there's a way to save our people...
我一定会找到
I'll find it.
别动她
Take it easy on her.
别废话
Don't talk.
明白吗
Understand?
你还好吧
Are you okay?
还好
Yeah.
我们被抓之前
You know, before we were caught...
你说我们需要
You said that we needed
把一切事物扳回原来的轨道
To put things back the way they were supposed to be.
我不明白你的意思
What did you mean by that?
如果我们能按Faraday说的做
If we can do what Faraday said...
我们的飞机就不会坠落
Our plane never crashes...
815航班会在洛杉矶安然降落
Flight 815 lands in los angeles.
我们到这里以后所有死去的人
And everyone we lost since we got here...
现在应该都还活着
They'd all be alive.
那我们俩呢
And what about us?
我们只是
We just...
依旧过着自己的生活
Go on living our life
只因为我们素未谋面吗
Because we've never met?
我们经历过的种种不幸
All the misery that we've been through...
都会烟消云散  就像从未发生过
We'd just wipe it clean. never happened.
不全是不幸
It was not all misery.
那也够人受的
Enough of it was.
我击中的那个人
The man I shot...
他要氢弹干什么
What did he need the bomb for?
告诉我  他要那氢弹做什么
I need you to tell me why he wanted the bomb.
我说了你也不会信
I don't think you'd believe me if I did.
我17岁时
When I was 17 years old,
我带一个年轻人去找炸弹
I took a young man to the bomb.
接着他告诉我  如果我们把它给埋了
He proceeded to tell me that if we buried it underground,
将会是一大壮举
Then things would work out splendidly.
我问他我为什么如此肯定
When I asked him how he could be so sure...
他说他来自未来
He said that he was from the future.
说完就消失了
And then he disappeared,
就在我眼前消失得无影无踪
Right in front of my bloody eyes.
十分钟前
Ten minutes ago,
我击中了那人的背部
I shot that man in the back.
他临死前
And before he... died...
告诉我
He told me that he...
他说是我儿子
He said he was my son.
告诉我详情
Explain to me...
我保证我会深信不疑
And you have my word I will believe you.
这怎么会是我的笔记  我却一点没印象
How is this my handwriting if i don't remember writing it?
因为你还没动笔
Because you haven't written it yet.
我知道这很难理解
I know this is hard to understand,
但
But...
你刚才做的事
What you just did...
是场意外
It was an accident,
有办法可以挽回这一切
And I think that there's a way for you to take it all back.
什么
What?
你儿子回到这里
Your son came back here
是因为他找到了破解之法
Because he had figured out a way to change things.
他不必死
He doesn't have to be dead.
你也没必要杀了他
You don't have to have killed him.
如果我们按照那篇日志上记载的做
If we do what's written in that journal...
这一切就不会发生
None of this will have happened.
他是不是不知所云
Does he know what he's talking about?
他自认为头脑清楚
He thinks he does.
那好吧  我带你去找炸弹
All right then, I'll take you to the bomb.
只是
Just...
可我得先说清楚
One small issue, however.
20多年前我们把炸弹埋在地下
We secured it over 20 years ago underground.
可那时起
But since that time,
有人在那里建造了整个村庄
It appears that someone's built an entire village over it.
达摩组织吗
The dharma initiative?
但是
However...
看来你们俩
It appears that you two
也是他们的成员
Have been passing yourselves off as members, so...
我想你们的行动会相对容易一些
I suppose coming and going will be relatively simple.
没你想像中那么简单
Ah, it might be a little bit more complicated than that.
那女人  现在在哪里
That woman-- where is she now?
找我的律师谈
Call my lawyer.
Stuart  你到底在干什么
Stuart! what the hell are you doing?
我在逼供  她在哪里
I'm getting answers. where is she?!
住手  该死  住手
Hey. hey! stop! damn it, stop.
我命令你  现在还是我说了算
That is an order. i'm still in charge here.
不  以前是你说了算  Horace
No, you were in charge, Horace.
可我们要想保护自己人
But if we're gonna protect our people
和我们付出的所有艰辛劳动
And all the work we're doing here,
接下来的事  你是应付不过来的
You don't have the stomach for what happens next.
Phil
Phil.
Jim  给你最后一次机会
Okay, Jim, last chance.
你告诉我她在哪
You tell me where she is...
不然我就宰了你
Or so help me god, I will kill you.
现在准备招出来吗
You ready to talk now?
不
Nope.
相信我  Jim  我也厌倦了这样
Believe me, I'm gettin' tired of this too, Jim.
招了吧
So why don't you tell me
你女朋友带那孩子去了哪
Where your girlfriend took the boy?
把他带去投奔敌人了吗
She bring him to the hostiles?
你知道他们在那里吗
You know where they are?
住手
Stop!
-求你了  -你想让我住手吗
- Please! - You want me to stop?
那就回答我的问题
Then tell me what I want to know!
Stuart  求你了
Stuart, please.
我们认识有3年了
We have known each other for three years.
我们不是坏人  我们不是来伤害你的
We are not bad people! We are not here to hurt you!
Juliet
Juliet...
不要
Don't.
不管你说什么
Whatever you tell 'em,
他们都不会相信的
They ain't gonna believe you.
只会伤及无辜
It's only gonna get more people hurt.
我们在干什么
What are we doing, man?
打他没用  好吗  他不会招的
Beating him is pointless. Okay? He's not gonna talk.
我能敲开他的嘴
I can make him talk.
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
冷静冷静
Easy. Easy.
Phil  你死定了
You're a dead man, Phil.
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you.
Radzinsky先生
Mr. Radzinsky?
还是没有Miles和Jin的消息
There's still no sign of Miles or Jin.
但上星期新来的人
But the recruits from last week...
我从Amy那里找到了潜艇运载名单
I got their sub's manifest from Amy.
有三个人最后才临时加进来
There were three last-minute add-ons.
其中两人是枪击你的
They were the two people that shot at you--
Shephard和Austen  还有一人尚未查出
Shephard and austen-- and one guy we can't track down.
他一定也参与了这事
He's gotta be a part of this.
Hugo Reyes是谁
Who the hell is Hugo Reyes?
那个胖子
He's the fat guy.
营救计划是怎样的
So what's the rescue plan?
营救计划  我们正向海滩走
Rescue plan? we're heading to the beach.
不然你以为  为什么派你去拿食物
Why do you think we sent you for food?
但Sawyer和Juliet他们
but they got Sawyer and Juliet
他们有30人  都有枪
And there are 30 of them, and they all have guns.
我们只能自救  走吧
The only people we can rescue is our ourselves, so let's go.
我们不能坐视不管
We gotta do something.
Sawyer不会抛弃我们的
I mean, Sawyer would never leave us behind.
张博士  你在这做什么
Dr. Chang? What are you doing here?
我也想问你们这个问题
I could ask you the same question.
我们先问的
But we asked you first.
你们的朋友Faraday
Your friend Faraday
说你们来自未来
Said that you were from the future.
我想知道他说的是否属实
I need to know if he was telling the truth.
这太荒谬了
Dude, that's ridiculous.
你生于哪年
What year were you born?
1931年
Uh... 1931?
你46了吗
You're 46?
是啊
Yeah.
是的
Yes, I am.
那你朝鲜战争中参战了吗
So you fought in the Korean War?
没这回事
There's no such thing.
谁是美国总统
Who's the president of the united states?
好吧  我们是来自未来  抱歉
All right, dude, we're from the future. sorry.
那就是真的了吗
It's true then?
你是我儿子
You are my son?
是啊
Yeah, it's true.
你朋友  那个物理学家
Your friend--the physicist--
他让我撤离岛上的所有人
He also told me to evacuate everyone I could off the island.
他说
He said there was going to be a
天鹅站会有场巨大的事故
Massive accident at the Swan
这是真的吗
Now is that true?
目前为止他都是正确的
He's been right about everything so far.
如果Faraday要岛上所有人撤离
If Faraday said get people off the island...
我会照做
I'd do it.
那就但愿他头脑清醒
Well, then let's hope he knows what he's doing.
告诉我吧
Tell me something.
为什么这人看起来
Why is it that this man looks...
如此眼熟
Familiar to me?
Richard
Richard...
你和Erik跟我走
You and Erik are coming with me.
跟你去哪里
Going with you where?
给他松绑
You can untie them.
不介意让我们独处一会吧
Would you mind giving us a moment?
我带他们去找炸弹
I'm taking them to the bomb.
什么
What?
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
我很担心你
I'm worried about you.
你现在状态不好
Not in your condition.
他是谁
Who is he?
Jack  那是Charles Widmore
The man you're asking about, Jack, is Charles Widmore.
他和Eloise是
He and Eloise are...
爱情真复杂
Well, let's just say love can be complicated.
好的  我们走吧
All right. let's move out.
John
So, John...
你打算告诉我
You, uh, you ready to tell me
这三年你都去哪里了
Where you've been the last three years?
你真的不知道吗
You really don't know?
我只知道  当Ben转动了转轮
Well, i know that on the day that Ben here turned the wheel
你和我就站在一个木板上
That you and i were sitting on a log.
有强烈的白光和噪音
There was a bright light. there was a loud noise,
然后你就  就消失了
And then you just... you disappeared.
Richard你马上就可以看到
Well, Richard, you're just about
我也消失过的地方
to see where i disappeared too.
而当我们把事情完成
And after we're finished with that,
我要你带我去见Jacob
I'd like you to take me to see Jacob.
John  这不符合规矩
That's... not how it works, John.
真的吗  Richard  会有什么问题吗
Is that true, Richard? is this gonna be a problem?
你刚回来而已  John
You just got back, John.
没必要那么着急就
There's no reason to rush into--
我现在是你们的带头人吧
I am the leader now. right?
是的没错  John
Yes, John. that's right.
好  那我要你带我去见Jacob
Good. then i would like you to take me to Jacob.
-你能带我去吗  -当然
-Can you do that? yeah  -of course.
非常好
Fantastic.
我们继续走  快要到飞机那里了
Let's keep moving. we're almost to the plane.
什么飞机
What plane?
一架走私海洛因的飞机
It's a beechcraft-- used to smuggle heroin.
从尼日利亚起飞  在这里失事
Flew out of nigeria, crashed here.
现在 你仔细听好了  Richard
All right, Richard, listen very carefully
因为你只有大概三分钟的时间
Because you're only gonna have about three minutes
-把事情做好  -把什么做好
-To get this right.   -Get what right?
一个男的将要走出丛林
A man's about to walk out of the jungle.
但是他的脚被射伤了
He's been shot in the leg.
你需要这些把子弹取出来
You'll need this to get the bullet out.
我没听懂  John
Uh, i'm sorry, John. i'm not--
你现在仔细听好  这是最重要的一点
Now just listen. this is the important part.
你一定要告诉他
You're gonna need to tell him
他必须让所有离开岛的人回到岛上
That he has to bring everyone who left back to the island.
当他问该怎么办的时候
And when he asks how to do that...
你告诉他他必须死去
You tell him he's gonna have to die.
那个男的是谁  John
Who is that man, John?
我
Me.
Richard
Richard?
Richard...
到底发生了什么事
What is happening?
发生了什么  你会失血过多死去
What's happening is that you're bleeding to death.
我需要你把子弹取出来
I need to get the bullet out.
你怎么知道有子弹在我腿里
How did you know there was a bullet in my leg, Richard?
是你告诉我的  John
Because you told me there was, John.
不  不  不  我没有
No, no. no, i didn't.
是的  你将会告诉我的
Well... you will.
这种灵魂出窍的感觉很好吧
This must be quite the out-of-body experience.
感觉可以
Something like that.
你计算的天衣无缝  John
Your timing was impeccable, John.
你是怎么知道该什么时候出现在这里的
How did you know when to be here?
这个岛告诉我的
The island told me.
它从未告诉过你什么吧
Didn't it ever tell you things?
很明显它没告诉你Jacob在哪里啊  John
No, John. and clearly it hasn't told you where Jacob is,
否则你也不需要Richard告诉你
Or you wouldn't need Richard to show you
你从未见过他
you' ve never seen him
什么
What?
Jacob  你从未见过他
Jacob. you've never seen him, have you?
刚才发生了什么
What just happened?
你去了哪里
Where did you go?
去把指南针还给Richard
To give Richard his compass back.
你要这个子弹吗
You want the bullet?
你留着吧
Keep it.
一切还好吧
Everything go all right?
你的话还是挺有说服力的
Well, you-ou seemed pretty convinced,
尤其是当我说你将会死去的时候
Especially when i said you were gonna die.
让我欣慰的是这并没有发生
I'm certainly glad that didn't have to happen.
事实上  Richard  已经发生了
Actually, Richard, it did.
我们还是回到营地吧
We better get back to camp.
你需要撤离这个岛上所有的人
You need to evacuate the island
所有无关的人员
of all nonessen
你需要去...
And you need to do it...
这里发生了什么
What the hell is going on here?
张博士  你不是应该在天鹅站吗
Aren't you supposed to be at the swan right now, Chang?
我们应该在20个小时内把井打通
We're supposed to break ground in less than 20 hours.
我们受到了威胁
We're under imminent threat.
如果我们开始钻井
If we start drilling,
将很有可能会发生灾难性的事件
There's a high probability of a cataclysmic accident.
我们按照计划继续钻井
We are drilling and on schedule.
Horace你来负责这里
Horace, you're in charge.
他再也不是负责人了
he's not in charge anymore.
这是我的决定  我说的算
This is my decision, and it's been made.
-我们继续钻井  -把我们带到潜水艇去
-We keep working.   -put us on the sub.
他是对的  这里不安全了
He's right. it ain't safe.
把妇女孩子带到潜水艇去
Put the women and children on the sub
让他们离开这里
And get 'em the hell out of here.
如果你把我和Juliet带到潜水艇
And if you put me and Juliet on the sub with 'em...
我们会告诉你一切
We'll tell you anything you wanna know.
这样可以了吧  亲爱的
You okay with that, sweetheart?
是的
Absolutely.
Jim你也进潜水艇吧
You want on that sub, Jim?
画个地图给我
Draw me a map.
我要知道敌人的具体位置
I wanna know exactly where the hostiles are.
你们两个会游泳吗
You two know how to swim?
我们就在上面看看不行吗
Why don't we just go around it?
不  我们要下去
No, dear, we need to go in.
潜到水底进入隧道
We have to swim under the pond to get to the tunnels.
我不去
I'm not going.
什么
What?
我要回去找其他人  我...
I'm gonna go back and find everyone else. i...
我这次不能再跟你走了Jack
I can't go any further with you Jack. not this time.
Kate  你现在不能回去  他们认识我们
Kate, you can't go back there now. they know about us.
他们会杀了我们的
They... they tried to kill us.
那你打算怎么办
And what are you trying to do?
再见  Jack
Bye, Jack.
哪都别去
You're not going anywhere.
不  别这样
No, you don't need to do that.
我们没有跟陌生人说出秘密
We're not in the habit of telling our secrets
然后让他们随便就走的习惯
To strangers, then just letting them saunter off.
我才不关这些  我要走了
You know, i don't care i just wanna leave.
把枪放下  都放下枪
Look, just put the gun-- step ay!
别开枪  如果她想走  就让她走
Hey! i said stop! if she wants to leave, she can leave!
我们在干什么  Eloise
What are we doing here, eloise?
那个人刚刚杀了一个我们的人
That man just killed one of our own people,
可是你却好像什么都没发生一样
And you're acting like it doesn't matter.
如果他们说的那些事
If these people are right
都是真的  Richard  就没事了
About what they're about to do, richard, it won't matter.
他们要干什么
And what are they about to do?
你告诉我
So you're telling me
你要把我们过去三年的生活都删除
You're going to erase the last three years of our lives?
我们可以改变这些事  Sayid
We can change things, sayid.
我不知道你们能不能
I don't know if you're aware of this
可是我已经改变了一些事了
But i've already changed things.
我杀了Benjamin Linus
I killed benjamin linus,
可是我们现在还在这  那是因为你没杀他
And we're all still here. it's because you didn't kill him.
Sawyer和我把他带到了岛上居民那里
Sawyer and me took him to the others
他们可以救他
So that they could save him.
你为什么这么做
Why did you do that?
我为什么这么做
Why did i do that?
向孩子开枪 投氢弹
Since when did shooting kids and blowing up hydrogen bombs
难道就对了嘛
Become okay?
我们的三个人
The three of us disappeared off
放弃了那个计划
that plane and
因为只有这样我们才能改变未来
Ended up now, because this is our chance to change things.
可是如果你们错了  岛上的所有人都会死
And if you're wrong, then everyone on the island dies.
你明白吗
Do you understand that?
我没有错 Kate 这就是我在这的原因
I'm not wrong kate, this is it, this is why we're here.
这是我们的命运
This is our destiny.
知道你说话的语气像谁吗
Do you know who you sound like?
因为他也疯了  Jack  你是这样说的
Because he was crazy, too, jack. you said so yourself.
好吧  或许是我错了
Well, maybe i was wrong.
不  你是对的
No, you were right.
我要回去找他们
I'm going back to find the rest of our people,
我不能阻止你  他们也许可以
Because if i can't stop you, then maybe they can.
潜艇将在30分钟内离开
The submarine departs in 30 minutes.
所有撤离人员  请马上到码头上来
All evacuees, please proceed to the dock.
快点  Charlotte  跟我来
Come now, charlotte. stay with me.
这太可笑了  我可以帮你
This is ridiculous. i can help you.
不  Lara  你帮不了我  离开这
No, lara, you can't. just go over there.
我要你现在马上离开
I want you to leave now!
为什么他对她喊  老兄
Why is he yelling at her, dude?
这是他让她走的唯一方法
It's the only way he can get her to leave.
对不起  伙计
Sorry, man.
我们最好马上走
We'd better get going.
等等  等一会
Wait! whoa! whoa! wait--wait a second.
是Jim和Juliet
It's jim and juliet.
为什么那些人
Why the hell are they...
要把他们放到潜艇上
Putting them on the sub?
别担心  没事的
Don't worry. it's gonna be okay.
Sawyer会有办法的  对吗
Sawyer always has a plan, right?
我们会买下微软
We'll buy microsoft.
什么
Excuse me?
这样我们就能在78届超级杯赛上下注小牛队
Then we'll bet the cowboys in the '78 super bowl.
我们会变的很富有
We're gonna be rich.
对不起
Look, i'm sorry.
我应该听你的
I should've listened to you
三年前让你上这艘潜艇
When you wanted to get on this sub three years ago.
很高兴你现在对我说这些
I'm glad you talked me out of it.
快点  Lafleur  进去
Come on, lafleur. get in.
女士优先
Ladies first.
终于解脱了
Good riddance.
如果在那边我没见到你
If i don't see you the other side,
我不会怪你的
I won't blame you.
深吸一口气  跟上Richard
Now take a deep breath and follow richard under.
在石头下面
There's an opening in the bottom
有一个入口
of the rocks a獴?鷐???
比我想的远多了
That was a lot further than i thought it was.
我们在哪
Where are we?
隧道
The tunnels.
我们怎么把炸弹带出这里
You wanna tell me how we're gonna get a bomb out of here?
怎么带进来的就怎么带出去
The same way we brought it in.
你不会是指通过池塘带出去吧
I assume you don't mean through the pool.
这可是12英尺长  40000磅的氢弹
It's a 12-foot long, 40,000-pound hydrogen bomb.
不  不是从池塘
No, not through the pool.
没想到你也来了
I didn't think you'd come.
如果这样有用的话  我们都会得救的
Well, if this works, you might just save us all.
如果没有用呢  至少会让我们从痛苦中解脱出来
And if it doesn't? at least u'll put us out of our misery.
好了  我们开始吧
All right. let's get started.
我给你准备了一个帐篷  John
I'll have a tent prepared for you, john.
我们明早第一件事就去那
We'll get going first thing in the morning.
我想我们现在就可以出发
I thought we could leave right now.
现在
Now?
我很性急
I'm eager.
我们可以听你吩咐  但也许我们
We can do whatever you want, but maybe the two of us
该去我帐篷里面讨论一下
Should go to my tent and talk about
所有人都在这里吗
Is this everyone?
神庙那里还有另一组人  但
Well, there's another group at the temple, but--
如果你不介意
Well, if you don't mind,
我现在想和每个人都谈谈
I would like to talk to everyone here now.
当然可以  随便
Of course. Be my guest.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
我叫John Locke
My name is John Locke.
有人告诉我
I've been told that...
有段时间
For some time,
你们要听从一个叫Jacob的人
You all have been accepting orders from a man named Jacob.
是的  非常奇怪
And yet, oddly enough,
似乎没人真正见过他
It seems that no one has actually seen him.
现在我肯定对于  为什么他的存在
Now I'm sure there are very good reasons
和他到底在哪  都是秘密  这都有合理原因
Why his existence and where abouts are secret.
而我不知道原因到底是什么
I just don't know what they are.
老实跟你们说
And to be honest with all of you,
如果有人要命令我们该做什么
If there's a man telling us what to do,
我要知道他是谁
I want to know who he is.
那个人  Jacob  他能告诉我们
This man--Jacob? Can he tell us
如何把Jin和我们其他人带回这里吗
How to bring Jin and the rest of our people back here?
绝对可以
Absolutely.
Richard已经答应告诉我们该去哪里
Richard has agreed to show us where we need to go.
那么我现在就要去见Jacob
So I'm gonna go and see Jacob right now.
而且我希望大家都和我一起去
And I'd like all of you to come with me.
我开始觉得John Locke会是个麻烦
I'm starting to think John Locke is gonna be trouble.
你凭什么认为我会杀他呢
Why do you think I tried to kill him?
我们两分钟后离开
We're shovin' off in two minutes.
如果你们不给我们带来麻烦的话我会很感激的
Appreciate it if you didn't cause us any trouble.
Nemo  我们不会的
Wouldn't think of it, Nemo.
我们到了安娜堡市后该干什么呢
What are we gonna do en we get to Ann Arbor?
我们不去安娜堡市
We ain't going to Ann Arbor.
-你是什么意思  -这些人又不是警察
- What do you mean? - These guys ain't cops.
他们在现实世界没有权利管我们
They got no authority over us back in the real world
所以不管我们在哪里上了岸
So once we dock wherever we dock...
我们就自由了
We're free.
现实世界
"Real world."
我甚至不记得那是什么意思了
I don't even know what that means anymore.
过来
Hey, come here.
无论发生什么事  我会支持你的记得吗
Whatever happens, I got your back, remember?
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you back.
拿好  别关了船舱
Hold on! Don't close the hatch!
Horace也想要她离开这岛
Horace wants her off the island, too.
我们到了安娜堡市再对付他们
We'll let Ann Arbor deal with them.
在她回来的时候捉到他的
Actually caught her coming back into town.
把他和其他人铐在一起
Cuff her over there with the others.
收起登船梯
Clear the bridge.
全体船员下仓  快点
All personnel, lay below on the double.
我们离开了  机房  准备
We're away. Engineering, take your stations.
潜艇可以航行
Boat is clear for sea.
全体船员就位  准备下潜
All men to your stations. Prepare to dive.
登船梯收起  所有船员下仓
Clear the bridge. All hands below.
主排水口准备
Stand by main vents.
下潜中
Diving position.
-下压货仓准备  -潜艇可以下潜
- Stand by on ballast tanks. - Ship has been cleared for dive.
重复  潜艇可以潜水  准备潜水
Repeat, ship has been cleared for dive. Stand by for dive.
潜艇下潜
Ship to dive.
二三号发动机正常  检查二号和三号
Clear engines two and three. test two and three.
Jack
Jack.
但这女人
That this woman's motivation
帮我们引爆氢弹的动机
In helping us detonate a hydrogen bomb
只是想消灭达摩组织
Is only to annihilate the dharma initiative.
-是的  但我还是相信她  -为什么
-Yes, but I still trust her. - Why?
因为30年后  就是她
Because 30 years from now, she's the one
告诉我们如何回到这岛上的
Who's gonna tell us how to get back to the island.
因为这个你就相信她
And that makes you trust her?
现在怎么办
Now what?
美好的一天  不是吗
Beautiful day, isn't it?
是的  目前为止
Yes... so far.
Richard有些顾虑
Richard had some concerns.
顾虑什么
Concerns about what?
这样像带着帮朝圣的人去见Jacob让他很不安
This pilgrimage to Jacob makes him uncomfortable.
他表示 对你自己知道与否
He's expressed...
自己到底在做什么
Reservations about whether or not
持保留意见
You know what the hell you're doing.
谢谢你告诉我这个  Ben
I appreciate you bringing this to my attention, Ben.
我知道我们过去有分歧  John
I know we've had our differences in the past, John,
但是现在我是你的手下
But I'm here to follow you now.
那么如果你要Jacob帮你重组你的手下
So if you need Jacob to help you reunite your people,
-我会做任何  -我对
- Then I'll do whatever-- - I'm not
让我们的人重聚没有兴趣
Interested in being reunited with my people.
什么意思  你告诉Sun
What do you mean? You told sun--
我知道我告诉了她什么
I know what I told her,
但那不是我们要去找Jacob的原因
But that's not why we're going to Jacob.
那为什么我们要去找Jacob
Then why are we going to Jacob?
因为那样我可以杀了他
So I can kill him.